<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hosting &amp; 部署 on HUGO</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/</link><description>Recent content in Hosting &amp; 部署 on HUGO</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deployment with Rclone</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/deploymentwithrclone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/deploymentwithrclone/</guid><description>Deployment with Rclone # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/deployment-with-rclone/ If you have access to your web host with SFTP/FTP/SSH/HTTP(DAV), you can use rclone to incrementally deploy your entire Hugo website. Assumptions # A web host running a web server. This could be a shared hosting environment or a VPS. Access to your web host with any of the protocols supported by rclone, such as SFTP. A functional static website built with Hugo Deploying from</description></item><item><title>Deployment with Rsync</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/deploymentwithrsync/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/deploymentwithrsync/</guid><description>Deployment with Rsync # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/deployment-with-rsync/ If you have access to your web host with SSH, you can use a simple rsync one-liner to incrementally deploy your entire Hugo website. Assumptions # A web host running a web server. This could be a shared hosting environment or a VPS. Access to your web host with SSH A functional static website built with Hugo The spoiler is that you can deploy your</description></item><item><title>Host on 21YunBox</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hoston21yunbox/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hoston21yunbox/</guid><description>Host on 21YunBox # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-21yunbox/ Host your Hugo site with 21YunBox’s blazing fast Chinese CDN, fully-managed SSL and auto deploys from Gitee. 21YunBox is a fully-managed cloud platform dedicated to make web deployment easy within the Chinese Great Firewall where you can host static sites, backend APIs, databases, cron jobs, and all your other apps in one place. It provides blazing</description></item><item><title>Host on AWS Amplify</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonawsamplify/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonawsamplify/</guid><description>Host on AWS Amplify # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-aws-amplify/ Develop and deploy a cloud-powered web app with AWS Amplify. In this guide we’ll walk through how to deploy and host your Hugo site using the AWS Amplify Console. AWS Amplify is a combination of client library, CLI toolchain, and a Console for continuous deployment and hosting. The Amplify CLI and library allow developers to get up &amp;amp; running with</description></item><item><title>Host on Azure Static Web Apps</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonazurestaticwebapps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonazurestaticwebapps/</guid><description>Host on Azure Static Web Apps # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-azure/ Deploy Hugo to Azure Static Web Apps and automate the whole process with Github Action Workflow Azure Static Web Apps is a service that automatically builds and deploys full stack web apps to Azure from a Git repository, using GitHub Actions or Azure DevOps. The following documentation covers how to use GitHub Actions for the deployment. If you are using Azure DevOps,</description></item><item><title>Host on Cloudflare Pages</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostoncloudflarepages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostoncloudflarepages/</guid><description>Host on Cloudflare Pages # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-cloudflare-pages/ Cloudflare Pages can host your Hugo site with CDN, continuous deployment, 1-click HTTPS, an admin GUI, and its own environment variables. Cloudflare Pages are super fast, always up-to-date, and deployed directly from your Git provider (currently supports only GitHub and GitLab). Cloudflare Pages docs have a detailed tutorial on how to deploy a Hugo site.</description></item><item><title>Host on Firebase</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonfirebase/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonfirebase/</guid><description>Host on Firebase # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-firebase/ You can use Firebase’s free tier to host your static website; this also gives you access to Firebase’s NOSQL API. Assumptions # You have an account with Firebase. (If you don’t, you can sign up for free using your Google account.) You</description></item><item><title>Host on GitHub</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostongithub/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostongithub/</guid><description>Host on GitHub # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-github/ Deploy Hugo as a GitHub Pages project or personal/organizational site and automate the whole process with Github Actions GitHub provides free and fast static hosting over SSL for personal, organization, or project pages directly from a GitHub repository via its GitHub Pages service and automating development workflows and build with GitHub Actions. Prerequisites # Create a GitHub account Install Git Create a Hugo site and</description></item><item><title>Host on GitLab</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostongitlab/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostongitlab/</guid><description>Host on GitLab # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-gitlab/ GitLab makes it easy to build, deploy, and host your Hugo website via their free GitLab Pages service, which provides native support for Hugo. Assumptions # Working familiarity with Git for version control Completion of the Hugo Quick Start A GitLab account A Hugo website on your local machine that you are ready to publish BaseURL # The baseURL in your site configuration must reflect</description></item><item><title>Host on KeyCDN</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonkeycdn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonkeycdn/</guid><description>Host on KeyCDN # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-keycdn/ Accelerate your Hugo site globally with a KeyCDN integration. This tutorial shows you how to set up your static site as a GitLab page behind a KeyCDN pull zone. KeyCDN provides a multitude of features to help accelerate and secure your Hugo site globally including Brotli compression, Let’s Encrypt support, Origin Shield, and more. Assumptions # You already have a Hugo</description></item><item><title>Host on Netlify</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonnetlify/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonnetlify/</guid><description>Host on Netlify # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-netlify/ Netlify can host your Hugo site with CDN, continuous deployment, 1-click HTTPS, an admin GUI, and its own CLI. Netlify provides continuous deployment services, global CDN, ultra-fast DNS, atomic deploys, instant cache invalidation, one-click SSL, a browser-based interface, a CLI, and many other features for managing your Hugo website. Assumptions # You have an account with GitHub, GitLab, or Bitbucket. You have completed the Quick</description></item><item><title>Host on Render</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonrender/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostonrender/</guid><description>Host on Render # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-render/ Host your Hugo site for free with Render’s global CDN, fully-managed SSL and auto deploys from GitHub. Introduction # Render is a fully-managed cloud platform where you can host static sites, backend APIs, databases, cron jobs, and all your other apps in one place. Static sites are completely free on Render and include the following: Continuous, automatic builds</description></item><item><title>Hosting on Azure Static Web Apps</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostingonazurestaticwebapps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hostingonazurestaticwebapps/</guid><description>Hosting on Azure Static Web Apps # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-azure-static-web-apps/ Learn how to deploy a Hugo application to Azure Static Web Apps. You can create and deploy a Hugo web application to Azure Static Web Apps. The final result is a new Azure Static Web App with associated GitHub Actions that give you control over how the app is built and published. You’ll learn how to create</description></item><item><title>Hugo Deploy</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hugodeploy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/hostingdeployment/hugodeploy/</guid><description>Hugo Deploy # https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hugo-deploy/ You can upload your site to GCS, S3, or Azure using the Hugo CLI. You can use the &amp;ldquo;hugo deploy&amp;rdquo; command to upload your site directly to a Google Cloud Storage (GCS) bucket, an AWS S3 bucket, and/or an Azure Storage container. Assumptions # You have completed the Quick Start or have a Hugo website you are ready to deploy and share with the world. You</description></item></channel></rss>