<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>工具 on HUGO</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/</link><description>Recent content in 工具 on HUGO</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EditorPlug-ins</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/editorplug-ins/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/editorplug-ins/</guid><description>Editor Plug-ins for Hugo # https://gohugo.io/tools/editors/ The Hugo community uses a wide range of preferred tools and has developed plug-ins for some of the most popular text editors to help automate parts of your workflow. The Hugo community uses a wide range of preferred tools and has developed plug-ins for some of the most popular text editors to help automate parts of your workflow. Sublime Text # Hugofy. Hugofy is</description></item><item><title>Frontends</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/frontends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/frontends/</guid><description>Frontend Interfaces with Hugo # https://gohugo.io/tools/frontends/ Do you prefer a graphical user interface over a text editor? Give these frontends a try. enwrite. Enwrite enables evernote-powered, statically generated blogs and websites. Now posting to your blog or updating your website is as easy as writing a new note in Evernote! Lipi. Lipi is a native GUI frontend written in Java to manage your Hugo websites. Netlify CMS. Netlify CMS is</description></item><item><title>Migrations</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/migrations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/migrations/</guid><description>Migrate to Hugo # https://gohugo.io/tools/migrations/ A list of community-developed tools for migrating from your existing static site generator or content management system to Hugo. This section highlights some projects around Hugo that are independently developed. These tools try to extend the functionality of our static site generator or help you to get started. Do you know or maintain a similar project around Hugo? Feel free to open a pull request</description></item><item><title>OtherProjects</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/otherprojects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/otherprojects/</guid><description>Other Hugo Community Projects # https://gohugo.io/tools/other/ Some interesting projects developed by the Hugo community that don’t quite fit into our other developer tool categories. And for all the other small things around Hugo: hugo-gallery lets you create an image gallery for Hugo sites. flickr-hugo-embed prints shortcodes to embed a set of images from an album on Flickr into Hugo. hugo-openapispec-shortcode A shortcode that allows you to</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/search/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/search/</guid><description>Search for your Hugo Website # https://gohugo.io/tools/search/ See some of the open-source and commercial search options for your newly created Hugo website. A static website with a dynamic search function? Yes, Hugo provides an alternative to embeddable scripts from Google or other search engines for static websites. Hugo allows you to provide your visitors with a custom search function by indexing your content files directly. GitHub Gist for Hugo Workflow.</description></item><item><title>StarterKits</title><link>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/starterkits/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:03:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://t.is-local.org/hugo/tools/starterkits/</guid><description>Starter Kits # https://gohugo.io/tools/starter-kits/ A list of community-developed projects designed to help you get up and running with Hugo. Know of a Hugo-related starter kit that isn’t mentioned here? Please add it to the list. The following starter kits are developed by active members of the Hugo community. If you find yourself having issues with any of the projects, it’s best to file</description></item></channel></rss>